Step 1: click (537, 661) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page is loaded. Currently, it shows a conversion from $1.00 USD to €0.84 EUR. To com
Step 2: click (720, 661) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page is loaded. The current conversion shows 1 USD to EUR. I need to: 1) Change the
Step 3: click (510, 661) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Xe Currency Converter page is loaded. The conversion interface shows '1
Step 4: find_and_click (789, 679) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page is loaded. The current conversion shows 1 USD = 0.84376762 EUR. I need to conve
Step 5: click (537, 661) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page with a currency dropdown menu open. The current amount field shows '$1.00' and
Step 6: click (720, 661) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '1' in the 'From'
Step 7: find_and_click (784, 679) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '1' and the conver
Step 8: find_and_click (664, 679) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page with a currency dropdown menu open. The amount field currently shows '$1.00' in
Step 9: click (570, 661) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '$1.00' in the 'From' section. I need to clic
Step 10: click (720, 661) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '1' in the 'From'
Step 11: click (720, 661) [OK]\NLooking at the screenshot, I can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '1' in the From se
Step 12: find_and_click (694, 685) [OK]\NI can see the Xe Currency Converter page. The amount field currently shows '1' in the From section. I've been clicking r